planner5d.com 2017-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Planner 5D

(Version 01. April 18th 2012) 

The security of your personal information is important to us. We do not hold any liability for any personal data or any sensitive information you provided. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while our goal to use commercially acceptable ways to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee it is absolutely secure. Please keep it in mind before submitting any information about yourself. Please note that information that you voluntarily make public in your user profile, or which you disclose by posting comments or inserting of the Content will be publicly available and viewable by others. We do not hold any liability for any information that you voluntarily choose to be public through such and/or other explicit actions. 

We only use personal information collected through the PLANNER- 5D project and our Services for the purposes described in the Terms (www.planner5d.com/terms). For example, we may use information we collect: 

to provide our Services or information you request, and to process and complete any transactions; 

respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests, and complaints and provide customer service; 

to monitor and analyze Planner5D project usage and trends, and to personalize and improve Planner5D project and our users’ experiences on our sites, such as providing ads, Content, Materials, or features that match their profiles or interests, and to increase PLANNER- 5D project functionality and user friendliness; 

to send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, our site; and for any other purpose for which the information was collected. 

We will not share the personal information we collect from you through Planner5D project or our Services with third parties, except as described in the Terms. For example, we share information as follows: 

with service providers who are working with us in connection with the operation of our site or our Services; 

when you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you on Planner5D project that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information; 

when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants or court orders; 

You might be interested in inviting random people, whom you do not know but with whom you are interested in communicating through our products. In this event, please make sure you truly wish to share any of your information or data with such a person. Once you provide the information to such a person, we will not be able to guarantee that this person will not use this information against you, trade it or misuse it in any other way. We will not be able to prevent such misuse, nor will we be liable for it. We will only be able to block the account or delete the account of any user who violate our Privacy policy. However, once any information is provided by you directly to any person which is your friend or not through our products, we are not responsible for any consequences. 

During registration you are required to give information in/through Facebook account. We use this information to verify that you are a real person interested in using such site features for their designed purpose. 

Certain information about users can be gathered automatically and stored inside log files. This information might include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, the browser type, Internet service providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating systems, date/time stamps, and clickstream data. However, this information doesn't identify individual users and we use it exclusively to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track user movements around the site as a whole to improve the services provided. We do not link this automatically-collected data to any personally identifiable information. 

Your information with limited access rights (including personal information) can only be accessed by our authorized employees or consultants or the concerned group entities that need to have access to this data in order to be able to fulfill their given duties. However, we shall take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal data provided to it or collected by it with due observance of the applicable obligations and exceptions under the relevant legislation. 

We will retain your information for as long as is necessary to: fulfill any of the Services we provide or comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts. 

If we do decide to change our Privacy policy, we will post any changes to this privacy statement so that you are all aware of what information we collect, how we use that information, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy policy statement at any time, so please review it relatively frequently. 

If we make any changes to this Privacy policy, we will notify you here: www.planner5d.com/pp. 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy policy, please contact us at: [hello@planner5d.com](mailto:'hello@planner5d.com'). 

This Privacy policy of the Planner5D project is a legal part of the Terms of Service of the Planner5D project.
